Max!
Come here.
Let's not make the sisters wait.
Her name is Frey.
She's new here too.
Can you read?
This is a giraffe. They lived in Africa.
You can read?
Yes.
There are many robot servers, and they serve you all day.
If you live there, you'll never get sick, or old.
I'll take us there, one day.
-Really?     -Yes, I promise.
Frey and Max.
Forever.
Max, are you stealing again?
It breaks my heart. Why do you do it?
To save up ?
You want to buy a ticket to go up there?
That place is not for you, or me.
It's not fair, sister.
Why can't I go?
There are things in life that can't be explained.
We just have to accept them.
But one thing I know for sure.
You're a very special person.
One day you'll do something marvellous.
You were born for it.
My little Max.
Max, muy bueno!
Off to work, huh? Gotta get up early, to work that line.
Wanna make the world a better place?
That's real funny, I have a job. Chistoso.
Por favor ninos! You think I got money?
Do I look like I have money?
How about you, you got a little money?
Come on, whatta you got in there?
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's 5 bucks. Hey, wait a minute. I got 5 bucks, I'm rich.
I can buy my ticket to Elysium, huh?
Alright.
Please form an orderly queue. Your bus has arrived.
I don't have anything.
Checked. Move on.
Morning, Officer.
Extensive criminal history. Multiple felonies. What's in the bag?
Hair products, mostly.
I'm just fucking with...
Hey... I'm just going to work, man. There's nothing in the fucking bag.
Come on, I...
Misdemeanor: citizen disobedience.
Just going to work, man. Come on.
-Checked.     -Nothing in there, is it?
Zero-tolerance policy applies to all citizens.
No shit?
You must report immediately to your parole officer.
Thank you, Citizen.
No, thank you.
Frey, fracture in bed 2.
Max?
Frey...
I thought you were...
-When did you get back?     -Been back for a while.
-I see things haven't changed.     -No, this wasn't even my fault.
Of course not.
-Let me have a look.     -How is it?
Pretty bad break.
So you're a nurse, huh? You did it!
Yeah.
That's great.
You still stealing cars?
No, God, I don't do any of that stupid shit anymore.
I work at Armadyne. On the line, you know? Working...
-Frey, they need you up on the 3rd floor.     -Be right there.
-So, you know, now that you're back...     -Just a second.
Just a second.
Dominica, can you take over here?
Hey, listen. Now, you know, 'cause you're back and everything.
Max, I'm so sorry I have to go.
It's good to see you. Stay out of trouble.
I do.
Look...
I know why you left the neighborhood, I understand.
If I was as smart as you I would have left too.
Have dinner with me. Just...
I'll settle for a coffee.
-No.     -Aww.
Have I gotta break my other arm to get attention?
-Stop.     -...'cause I will do that.
My life is complicated, Max.
I just, I... I miss you.
-My shift ends at 8 on Wednesday, OK?     -Yeah, all right.
-Coffee.     -Yeah, coffee. Right.
Get out of here.
All parolees must have weapons inspection
Hello.
Before we start, I'd just like to explain...
Max da Costa, violation of Penal Code 2219. Today at bus stop 34-B.
Yes, that's exactly what I wanted to talk to you about.
See I believe there's been a misunderstanding.
Immediate extension of parole by a further 8 months.
Wait, What? No, no, I can explain what happened.
I just made a joke. And, you know...
Stop talking.
Police officers noted violent and antisocial behavior.
We regrettably must extend parole.
Elevation in heart rate detected.
-Would you like a pill?     -No!
Thank you, what I'd like to do is expl...
Stop talking.
Personality matrix suggests a 78.3% chance of regression to old behavior patterns.
Grand theft auto, assault with a deadly weapon,
resisting arrest.
-Would you like to talk to a human?     -No, I am OK. Thank you.
-Are you being sarcastic and/or abusive?     -Negative.
It is a federal offense to abuse a Parole Officer.
Understood.
Hey, da Costa!
-You're late for your shift.     -Yeah man, I had a little thing...
No, no. You can't work with that. You're out.
No, no, I'm good, man. I can work.
It's coming off later today. I'm fine.
-You're good?     -I'm good!
OK, I'm docking you half a day.
-Yeah, alright.     -You're lucky to have this job.
No weapons detected. You are clear for entry.
Please keep your workstation tidy.
A tidy workstation is an efficient workstation.
Hey check it out, man. I think he likes you.
Think he got his face peeled today? He looks good.
Attention: all workers must reach weekly quotas.
Please report any unsafe activity to your supervisor.
If we don't have a clear path to up-side,
our investors are going to start losing a lot of confidence.
What do you think I've been doing here, on Earth?
D'you think I enjoy breathing this air?
-No, of course, but...     -I'm doing everything possible...
to restore profitability to this company.
The company that I built.
Now, if you will excuse me,
I have to not speak to you people any longer. Thank you.
Closing 34!
Firing 34.
Tag her, quick!
Let's go, we don't have much time.
We have 3 transporter codes, Spider.
OK, pull'em up on screen.
Codes have been accepted.
Fire up the shuttles!
We're going up!
-Welcome.     -Hello, ma'am.
-Take a look at the garden.     -We will, thank you.
-Hello, Madame Delacourt.     -Hello.
Hi, Ivan, how you've grown.
Hi. You alright?
-Fine. Are the kids here?     -Yes, with Dominica.
I have a present for you. Wanna see? It's in the salon.
Go get it with your mother.
-It's, by the canape.     -OK
Bye.
Ma'am, would you care for a refreshment?
Demand's cancelled.
Sorry for disturbing you, ma'am. We have a number of undocumented ships inbound.
Good afternoon, Defense Secretary Delacourt.
3 undocumented ships are approaching Elysium airspace.
Emergency orders 6 and 7 are now in effect.
Protocol 22/B39...
Attention, incoming vessels.
You have made unauthorized entry into Elysium airspace.
-Dad!     -It's OK!
We will be forced to take immediate action.
You are in violation of Elysium airspace.
Standard warning didn't work.
15,000 kilometers and closing...
-What do you want us to do, ma'am?     -Activate Kruger.
Ma'am, according to Executive Order 355 we are unauthorized to use our assets on earth
I am authorizing you.
Yes, ma'am.
Agent 32--over. We are sending the packet--over.
Welcome, Agent Kruger!
10,000 kilometers and closing.
Sending coordinates to asset.
Three target data.
Shoot them down!
Green light, 21-B. Green light.
Missiles away!
Shit.
Impacto inminente. 10...
8... 7... 6...
5... 4... 3...
2... 1...
Two ships destroyed. 46 total casualties.
Impact in 5...
-Last missile was a miss.     -Ridiculous!
Only one made it.
Ma'am, the ship has breached our atmosphere.
First undocumented ship just touched down.
I want everyone coming out of that vehicle apprehendeded.
Identification confirmed.
Scanning.
Reconstruction process initiating.
No!
We have 32 arrests, 13 casualties, and 2 illegals at large, Ma'am.
Reconstruction complete.
You are under arrest, under the 68-C Immigration Act.
-All illegals are now in custody, ma'am.     -Yes.
Send them to deportation, Get them off this habitat.
Secretary Delacourt, please report to President Patel immediately.
Secretary Delacourt, report to President Patel.
What up, man? ?que te paso?
Lo es siempre, the police, man.
-Are you OK?     -Yeah, don't worry about it.
Max, I gotta talk to you. You know...
-No!     -What do you mean no?
You didn't even hear what I was gonna say.
-Alright, go ahead.     -OK.
You know the house of Doseta's up on the hill?
Yeah, the one with all the guns.
Yeah, they have five cars. New ones.
It's gonna be three of us. Tomorrow, at lunch.
-Lunch time?     -That's the plan?
Jesus Christ.
-You have a better plan?     -Yeah, just take one guy.
Go before the sun comes up. You take the two fastest cars.
Torch the batteries on the other ones.
Fuck you. Fuck you!
I got you, cojone!
Oh please. You're the best. Give me one year.
-I'm not going back to prison.     -One year, please!
Look at you! You used to be a legend, and now what?
The time is 5:50 am.
No weapons detected. You are clear for entry.
Closing 34!
Attention, doors are not aligned. Worker attend.
Hey, you're holding up the line.
No, no, I got a jam!
Attention: workers may not use the restroom more than once per sh...
-What've you done, da Costa?     -No, I'm just trying to reset.
Let me look.
-The pallet's pinched.     -Yeah, It didn't move.
-Just go in there.     -No, I mean...
Look, you go in there right now...
or we'll find someone who will, and you can go clean out your locker.
-Come on, man.     -No, no. That's the deal, OK?
In you go!
Let's go, people, back to work!
Fuck.
No, no, no, stop!
Hey!
Hey, come on, vamos!
Too late!
Extraction!
Sister, they beat me up.
I only want to live there.
See how beautiful it looks to us down here?
Yes.
Well, now...
See how beautiful we look to them up there.
Keep this.
Now it belongs to you.
So you never forget where you come from.
What happened?
You have been exposed to a lethal dose of radiation.
You will experience catastrophic organ failure.
In five days time, you will die.
What is going on? Why has production stopped?
-He's been exposed ...     -Don't breathe on me.
-Cover your mouth.     -I'm sorry, sir.
Does his skin fall off, or something?
I don't want to replace the bedding in there. Just get him out.
-Yes, sir.     -Right, thank you.
Mr. Carlyle, your shuttle is ready for departure.
Please sign this to receive medication.
Miporol--extremely potent.
Will keep you functioning normally until your death.
Please take one pill with each meal.
Thank you for your service.
At 15:00 hours yesterday you shot down two shuttles, killing 46 civilians.
Your mandate is to deal with illegals 'quietly'.
I am aware of that.
And then there's the use of this... agent.
A Mr. M. Kruger.
15 human rights violations...
Rapes, kidnappings, torture.
The man's been diagnosed with serious psychological issues.
We made it explicitly clear to you that we're no longer using sleeper agents.
Tell me something, President Patel.
Do you have children?
I'm not the one being reviewed here.
Then I will assume you do not.
Perhaps, if you did have children,
then you would behave in a manner
that is more conducive to the longevity of this habitat.
I understand, it is not the fashion to think and to act as I do.
I understand that perfectly.
But when they come for your house...
or the house you built for your children,..
and your children's children...
It won't be PR and campaign promises that keep them out.
It will be me!
I've heard enough! This is your final warning.
Any further unauthorized actions, and you will be removed from office.
And let's discharge this agent Kruger permanently.
All in favour?
Good. Effective immediately.
You want some beer?
You have been discharged from CCB.
Please return all weapons to local embassy.
Fuck your 'Politikster'! Fuck you!
Look...
Max...
Max!
What's wrong? What happened?
Jesus, let me help you. Let's go.
Max, what happened?
-Max, what happened?     -I shouldn't have gone in, man.
Gone in where?
I took a full dose, man.
A full dose.
You're gonna be OK. Let me help.
-You're gonna be OK, Max.     -They gave me Miporol, man.
They gave me... Miporol.
I got five fucking days! I only got five days!
You have to take this.
-They can fix this shit on Elysium, man.     -I know.
-I'm gonna go see Spider.     -Max, Max!
Take the pill!
There you go!
To see Spider, you need money.
I'll give you everything I have, but it's not enough for a ticket.
He's going to give me a ticket.
He's gonna give me a fucking ticket.
Frey, you know we've done everything we could to help your daughter.
But I had a meeting today with the board,
and they're recommending that we send her home with you.
How can I work here and leave her at home?
You know it can happen any minute, Dr. Faizel.
I know, if she has another seizure, of course bring her back here.
But until then she's discharged.
This isn't Elysium. We can't just heal her.
Max!
It's been a while, my brother!
How's life at the factory?
-I need to ask you a favour.     -What? I can't hear you. What?
I need a ticket. Up there. And an ID.
Yeah, sure sure.
Absolutely. You prefer aisle or window?
I'm being fucking serious, man.
Listen, I'm gonna come back and work for you.
Anything you need. I'll fucking pay it back.
You know what?
This... is...
priceless.
This is priceless.
Yeah, let me ask you a question.
Do you have any idea how many idiots
come in here saying the same kinda bullshit?
I got little kids coming here every day.
Max, if I were you, I'd get the fuck out of here, right now
Max, No...
I did 3 years for you.
Everything I did for you, you're gonna get me up there.
-Can you feel this?     -Go ahead and shoot.
I got so much radiation in my body right now,
you're probably getting a little sick yourself.
-You really dying?     -I'm fucking dying, motherfucker.
See this? It's over. I put the gun down.
Put the gun down! Put the gun down! Get out of here!
OK!
Listen, I've been looking for someone to take a job for me.
But no one here had the balls.
You said you'd do anything, right?
Max...
-OK.     -I'm OK.
This...
my friend,
this can be your ticket up there.
One last job for me, you earn your way up.
What is it?
Take an Elysian asshole, right?
A billionaire who's down on Earth for some business...
He's, he's here for, whatever. We hijack him.
-Fuck that!     -Relax.
The guy's like much worse.
Forget his watch, forget his ride, forget all that shit.
This, is what you take.
Organic Information, right out of his head.
I'm talking about bank codes, passwords, login data...
Access to billions.
All you have to do is plug into his brain, download the data to yours with this baby,
and bring it to me.
This is crazy, Max.
Once we verify the data, I'll give you a one way ride, all expenses paid.
Even throw in some snacks and a drink.
All you have to do is walk into a house and use the med-bay, and you're cured.
Sandro will do the surgery. You know him?
-Fuck...     -Christ!
I'm good.
Actually, you seem all weak.
And fucked up, so...
You know what? I have...
This is crazy, let's get out of here, Please, listen to me.
What the fuck am I gonna do?
I'll have them install...
...this!
A third generation Axo-suit.
We hook this into your nerval system, and it'll make you as strong as a droid.
You're already under the knife, right?
Let's get out of here, please.
I want a 4 man team. But I pick them.
I'm sending my own data wrangler.
Brain to brain, that is real tough.
OK, but I'm taking Julio. He gets a ticket up there, same as me.
Yeah, sure.
OK, I'll go get the boys ready.
Wait!
It's gotta be John Carlyle.
The CEO of Armadyne, Carlyle?
That's the mark.
Secretary Delacourt, Mr. Carlyle has arrived.
You are here to persuade me to renew our Armadyne contracts, yes?
Astute as always.
Come with me.
I'm not interested in your little ideas.
I am interested in something much larger.
This habitat is dying.
There is a political sickness inside of it. A tumor that needs to be removed.
You and your company are in need of revenue that is drying up.
So...
You built the Torus.
Can you override the servers and place a new president in power?
A coup?
Are you suggesting a coup?
Is it possible?
I could write a reboot sequence.
It'd shut down the entire system, and at that point...
you can encode a new President, yes.
Then that is what you will do.
And you will have your contract secured for the next 200 years.
Missile Defense Batteries, Droids, everything we need, to protect our liberty.
all guaranteed, of course, by your new President.
Go! Get to work, Mr. Carlyle.
This is the guy.
-He's the guy?     -This is him.
Sit down.
We're gonna cut you up good, homie.
Play nice, amigo. Play nice.
Let's get him an ID first.
Give the chief one of my identification codes.
Get that ready.
Arm up.
Weonly have
What did you find?
And we'll merge it with the DNA. Now you fit in.
Like you were born there.
Now it's time for the real fun.
Hey, man.
Yo.
This gonna hurt?
Yeah bitch, it's gonna hurt.
It's gonna hurt good.
When we're done with you, you're gonna be a  ninja.
Mariana!...
Bring down the bone saw!
This ain't gonna kill me.
You'll be airight. Not bad.
Max.
I'm here.
We got this, man.
We got this?
Yeah!
Hey!
He's awake!
Made it, huh?
Surprise!
You can still jack off, alright?
How's everything going?
Ready to kick ass?
What the fuck did you do to me?
Gave you a way out.
Shit.
What's up, partner?
How's that suit working out for you?
That shit is tight!
Show me.
Hold this.
Is it a family heirloom?
Wait for it.
Air-bursting ammunition.
Designate your enemy...
and any round you fire will explode around a 5 meter kill radius.
And...
safe detonation rounds for this bad boy.
That'll work.
Move out!
Sir...
Your shuttle is ready.
Do you read me?
Yes.
Alright, here's the deal.
We'll wait outside the factory until we see the shuttle leave.
One of you opens an explosive round in it,
goes to the crash site and gets the data.
OK, copy that.
Alright now, let's go! Let's play ball!
You nervous?
-No.     -No?
I'm shitting myself with fear.
-I'm not gonna fucking die.     -No.
Go, go, go!
Acceleration to supersonic speed in 15 seconds.
Come on, come on, come on!
Critical engine failure.
Ma'am, we have an Elysium citizen on Earth in danger.
Data coming up now...
Citizen identified. John Carlyle. N8321...
I see you, motherfucker!
I have a situation here.
Kruger, do you read me?
Ah, Ms Delacourt. How lovely to hear your voice.
There's a citizen carrying sensitive brain data out of the city right now.
Some thieves are trying to hijack it.
What's in it?
That's classified.
You don't call a recently deactivated agent to retreive classified fucking information!
The government doesn't know about this, do they?
I can ask for whatever I want, can't I?
Please brace for impact
Please remain calm. You have sustained zero injuries.
Oh, that's a real comfort.
I've got one condition. I do this, I get re-instated.
Fine.
I've recommissioned 2 of your preferred agents.
Completely confidentially, of course. They should be at your position any second.
Send me the mission data.
Let's go, guys. Out of the cars!
Droids, there appears to be some type of wheeled vehicle, with one
Two occupants.
They are armed and I'd like them dead.
Droid!
It's jammed!
Identified, Max da Costa. Federal Parole number 61492-8-557.
It's jammed, man!
Got it!
He's reloading!
-Guys! We got the bastard!     -Go! I got you covered!
Go, go, go!
Don't fucking move.
Bring it!
There's another one!
Die, motherfucker!
Don't hit the mark!
No, no! He got hit!
Citizen has sustained a cardio-thoracic trauma.
Blood pressure is dropping.
-It's not in the head!     -Is he breathing?
-No, it's in the chest!     -Well, fucking good, man.
Hold his head, hold his head.
Let me see your brain.
Come on, Come on!
-Yes.     -Is it working?
Yeah, we're syncing.
You have no idea what you're doing.
One minute to target, sir.
We're syncing. Come on, baby, here we go.
It's gonna work. We got it.
It's a data heist, ma'am. They're downloading now.
Guys, we've got incoming.
Fuck me!
Come on, guys, hurry up.
That's a Raven. That's Military.
-Alright we got this, 97...98!     -Hurry up, they're coming.
-Almost there!     -99!
In! Here we go!
Shit! Data must be corrupted!
Wait. Hold on.
I can't read the data. It's scrambled! I can't read the data.
What?
-Come on, guys! We gotta move!     -What the fuck does 'scrambled' mean?
Fuck this!
No, No! Run it again! Run it another time!
-Get off me, man! I'm bailing!     -Please. Run it again.
Fuck you! Let's get out of here.
Where the fuck are you going, Sandro?
Let's get outta here! Goddamit!
C'mon man.
Get out of there! Let's go!
We gotta go! Come on! Come on!
Hey, boss, we got a runner.
Fire!
That's what I'm talking about!
Fuck, man!
Target moving south-southwest.
Move back! It's coming!
We got another one.
Again!
This is wrong! This is all wrong, man!
Going into holding pattern, sir!
Where do you think you're going?
Come on!
Fuck!
Motherfucker!
Come on!
No!
No, no!
No! Get up!
Get up!
No!
We've got one assailant leaving on foot, ma'am.
They have the data. Repeat:
The thieves have the data.
Apprehend the target at all costs. Do not damage his brain.
Let's go! We got a runner, boys!
The citizen has suffered catastrophic blood loss leading to cardiac arrest.
Time of death, 17:45.
Come on, where are you hiding?
What's that?
Looks like a herd of pigs, boss.
Fuck you, man! Find him!
Take us back to the crash site, to see what they left behind.
Roger, that.
Thanks.
Hey boss, I think you better come look at this.
This is a record of what we picked up
being transferred between Carlyle and the criminals.
That's why she wants it so badly.
He's got the keys to the kingdom in his fucking head!
Now we just need to find him.
Gonna let the girls out.
Searching grids 3 through 11.
I'm authorising a Full Containment Order.
Issue a No Fly Zone for Los Angeles.
-All of Los Angeles?     -The murderer's still out there.
Until we apprehend him, no one leaves the surface of that city.
What the f...?
Max.
-Hey, sweety!     -Hey.
We can go home.
Am I better?
I'm gonna get the car, OK?
Be right back.
Frey...
Max!
My God, what happened to you?
-Shit, I'm gonna get the medics.     -No, no!
-I can't go in there.     -Max!
-I can't go in...     -Max, listen, you need a doctor, OK?
People are looking for me. They're gonna kill me.
-I came here for you. I need your help.     -Max!
You've got to go through the system to get treatment.
Please help me. I don't wanna die.
Max!
Stay awake!
-I wanna see the man.     -Mama's gonna help him, OK?
Try and sleep.
Don't sleep!
You're too heavy for me. Max, help me!
Come on!
Max, you can do it, come on!
No, wait. Let's turn you over!
Max, Max, wait.
-Thank you.     -Who did this to you?
I don't know. I got-I got hurt at at work.
I had to take a job from Spider to try to get up there and get healed.
It went bad, now I'm in trouble.
Mommy?
Hey, sweety, come here!
Who is that man?
His name is Max. Mommy knew him when he was your age.
-It's Matilda.     -Hi!
You can go watch cartoons, OK?
I'll be right there.
I didn't know you had... I'm so sorry, I need to go.
-Wait, Max, you can not leave.     -I shouldn't have come here. I have to leave!
Max! She's dying. She's in the final stages of leukemia.
I told you my life complicated. I need you to help me.
-I've no idea how to do this.     -How to do what?
-Get her to Elysium.     -I can't help her. I...
I would if I could.
How about this? Fake citizenship. If you took her there,
-could you heal her with this?     -It doesn't work that way.
This is coded to me, it's locked to my DNA.
The people looking for me. They... You don't understand who these people are.
If they find me here, they will kill all of us.
The only thing I can do to help you is leave. I promise you.
-She's all I have.     -I'm sorry.
You have bandages.
Yeah. I got bandages.
What are you doing?
I don't want you to be sick. You wanna hear a story?
N.., ah...
There once was a meerkat who lived in the jungle.
He was hungry and he was small.
So small.
And the other big animals had all the food, 'cause they could reach the fruits.
So he made friends with a hippopotamus
OK, stop!
It doesn't end well for the meerkat.
Yes, it does 'cause he can stand on the hippopotamus' back
to get all the fruits that he wants.
-What's in it for the hippo?     -The hippo wants a friend.
I'm sorry.
Hey, boss.
I think we got him.
Yank this fucking cunt!
-Mommy, is everything OK?     -It's OK, sweety.
Clear!
What is this?
Good afternoon.
Sorry to come bursting into your home. Didn't mean to...
traumatize your young daughter.
Me and the boys here are looking for a young gentleman...
who was in this very house a moment ago.
We're hoping you can tell us where he went.
No.
I...
-I don't know where he is.     -I don't believe in ...
...committing violent acts in front of the kids.
So I just need you to close your eyes, sweetheart.
-It's OK.     -I really need you to tell me.
Hey?
-You remember now?     -Mommy!
Close your eyes, keep your fucking eyes closed.
Keep her eyes closed.
Please, I don't know where he is.
He was wounded, I helped him and he left.
Please!
D'you fucking hear that? No loyalty nowadays, hey?
What's this here?
-This a hospital you're running here?     -She's sick.
She's sick? Let me have a look at her... Alright!
-Don't touch her.     -See that? Protective instinct, here!
I said don't touch her!
I'm just trying to get a word with your child.
Don't touch her!
-Bring her. Come!     -Where are you taking her?
-Now I've got something you want.     -Sweety, it's OK.
It's OK, darling. It's OK.
Sit down! Shut up!
Stop!
No, no, don't shoot him! Put the gun down! Let him come!
-You got something, didn't you?     -What?
That's why they shut down the sky... what is it?
Wire transfers? Corporate intel? You gotta have something big in there!
No. I fucking got nothing, man!
It all got scrambled. Julio is dead. You owe me. Let's go fucking now!
We can't! The flight system is jammed!
Nobody is going up there.
-Until when?     -Till I don't fucking know.
-I gotta fucking get up there!     -Everyone needs to get up there.
My guys are working on it.
See if they have a hope in hell of ever getting back online.
But, for now...
Let's just take a look at that head of yours.
Get away from me, man!
Look at me, if they shut down the whole fucking sky,
for what's in your head...
Maybe the key to opening it could be in there too, right?
Come on.
Alright.
They will hunt you to the edge of the world for this.
What is it?
It's a reboot program for Elysium.
Whoever has this, has the power to override their whole system.
Open the borders...
Make everyone a citizen of Elysium.
This can save your life.
-We can save everyone.     -When can I go?
They're trying to hack through the signal jam, but soon...
-Don't bullshit me, when can we go?     -I dunno.
Five days... a week?
Fuck you, I don't have 5 days! I got hours.
My guys are working on it.
You're always working on it, You can't get me up there.
I don't know why you try sending people up there,
they just get fucking shot down.
Not with what's in your head! That's what I'm talking about!
We would control the system. We would be in charge!
We can change the course of fucking history!
Back up then.
What I have in my head, is worth a lot to them, right?
Don't do this.
If that falls into the wrong hands, they could shut us out for good.
Listen, man, I'm going up there right now.
If you can find me, and I'm healed, you can have all of this.
-But I'm not fucking dying.     -This is wrong, Max, don't do this.
Don't shoot him! Don't shoot him!
It's OK. It's OK.
I always wanted a wife.
Just couldn't quite settle down, you know? Too much temptation.
But you...
You make me ready to settle down.
You really make me want to settle down, baby.
-Holy shit, sir.     -Eh?
You better come take a look at this.
-What is it?     -Check this fucking oak.
Turn us around.
-Take it.     -Right, sir.
Open the door.
Stop right there, and you're gonna do exactly what I say.
Or I'm gonna blow my fucking head off, you understand?
Yeah!
You can have everything in my head!
Just take me up there, and get me in a med-bay.
-What I have is very valuable.     -We can fix you up.
Put you in a med-bay, Sort all this cock-up.
Let's go! We'll take you up there.
Weather's nice, air's nice and clean. Likely you'll dig it.
-Don't you fucking try anything!     -Step aboard!
Come meet the boys, come on!
Don't be shy, they won't bite.
Let me introduce you. This is Drakie. This is Max.
What is news?
Let's fly!
Yes, ma'am, we apprehended the subject.
-Open the skies, we're coming up.     -I'll expect you in 19 minutes.
-Cancel the No Fly Zone.     -Yes, ma'am.
Hold it...
Hold it. What is that? ...
Are we back? Marcelo! What the fuck is that? Are we back?
We're back online, Spider.
Frey...
I'm sorry. I'm gonna make this right.
-We've got him.     -Alright. Where is he?
He's leaving Earth... Heading to Elysium.
Manuel! Rico! Get weapons! Let's get up there.
Echo leader 234, requesting landing in sector 22.
Roger that Echo leader 234. You are clear for entry...
-I see you got the G-1 there.     -Hey, back the fuck up!
-Or what?     -I'll let it go.
What you gonna do? Huh?
I want what's in your head, boy. Kill him!
Grab him, Deck!
What do you want us to do, ma'am?
I want everyone coming out of that vehicle apprehended by Homeland Security.
Evacuate everyone on the level five clearence out of the building, now.
I warned you of this.
An unlicenced vehicle just crashed potentially threatening the Torus.
All because of your inability to act. Evacuate him.
-Get your hands off me.     -This is an act of war.
That puts the CCB under my control.
Now, if you'll let me do my job.
I'm sure you have a fund raiser to attend.
Let's go, sir.
Max!
Take me out of here, Max!
I'm trying!
Air quality reaching toxic levels.
Get me out of here!
It is recommended you exit the craft immediately.
Run!
Fuck!
2 Illegals heading northeast in zone 3
You deal with those two. I'll handle this pussy.
Welcome to the spectacular properties from your...
Error
No!
No citizen detected.
Please she's sick, help us. She's gone into a coma.
Please!
Shouldn't we remove this thing?
Can't, till we get all the data.
It's wired into him neurologically.
The data is intact, yes?
Data looks intact.
Warning
We can still pull this data out of him, which will kill him.
Oh, it's fine.
How long before you can download and turn the system online?
Not long, Ma'am.
Keep everything in a restricted cloud. Lock down all access.
Starting prep right now.
And get these two out of here.
Roger that.
Kurt, you wanna go get the boss' chicks?
Yeah, good.
Give them the runaround.
Keep them busy.
Got him!
Let's go!
Alright. 50 exabytes, buddy. Are you ready?
What are you taking out of him?
Hey! What're you doing to him?
What's gonna happen to him? Hey!
Rise and shine.
-Get up!     -Max.
Max. Max. Max!
Get in there!
Yes. Boss got fucked up, eh?
Ate that fucking grenade, eh!
His brain is fine. But he's gonna be pissed when he wakes up.
Remember what cock-up happened in India when he lost his hat?
Kruger.
Boss?
It's Crowe.
Where is he?
All right, all set. Let's reach the data.
I got the needle prepped. You wanna grab this?
Grab the needle! Grab the needle! Grab the...
-Where did they take the girls?     -The Armory.
Where the fuck is that?
Level three.
Lethal radiation poisoning detected. You require urgent medical attention.
You idiot! Do you realize what you've done?
You crashed an unlicensed vehicle into a suburban area.
Your orders were to keep this covert.
Do you even remember what that means?
Have you completely lost your mind? You're useless to me.
If the administration realized what we're doing,
they'd hang us both for treason.
For God's sake, Kruger! Are you listening to me?
Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm listening.
I'm sorry that we crashed the vehicle and ruined someone's lawn.
But nobody is gonna hang us for treason.
We do the hanging!
Put your hand on it, keep pressure on it.
How tough you be now, eh?
Right boys, Elysium is about to get its first proper president.
She needs some medical attention.
I was gonna heal your daughter.
But now, I'll make sure she's never healed.
Drakie, don't trust any of those politicians!
Clear out this whole building!
Thank you, boss.
I'm gonna find that little gangster.
I'm gonna take what's in his head. This place is mine now.
You want to come to my fucking house and play?
Let's play!
I'm going to annihilate that little motherfucker.
Hey!
What the hell was that?
All members of CCB please go to the nearest exit and proceed calmly to...
Go, go, go!
No.
Citizen deceased
Emergency systems are now online
Please follow indicated procedures
Spider!
Do you read me, Spider?
Max, where are you.
The thing in my head, it can make everyone a citizen here, right?
Yeah.
You know how to get it out, right?
Yes.
You're sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
OK, listen to me carefully.
Armory selected.
Set.
Turn me on.
OK.
Crowe, get rid of those two.
My pleasure, boss. My pleasure.
Where are you, Pikey? Where are you?
How is it, girl?
Let's play.
-Come on, I'll be nice. Gentle, I promise.     -No. Please.
-Come on.     -Get off me!
-Want me to hurt the girl?     -No.
Then come here.
Fuck!
She alive?
For now.
Stay behind me.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
I have a plan.
D'you hear that sound?
That's the sound of me coming for you.
I'll find you! I'll hunt you down!
Frey, we have to split up.
-What?     -Listen.
You're gonna go to the surface, OK? Take this.
Find a house, get her to a med-bay.
-Max, it won't work.     -Don't stop. Don't stop...
She doesn't have an ID. It doesn't work.
It will this time. I know how to fix it.
-Surface selected     -Go.
Come with me.
-I'm right behind you.     -No.
I promise.
OK, a mother and her daughter just went up in that elevator.
They're going to the surface headed for a med-bay.
Send one of your guys make sure they get there.
And we have our deal.
Right to a med-bay, man.
-Let's go.     -Let's go.
-Go, go, go!     -This way!
Hurry up, man.
...emergency lock down...
Almost there. Almost there.
What's that?
It's just a ... bitch!
That's what I'm talking about.
Fire has been detected...
Hold the door! Hold the door!
...have been shut down.
-Come on! Come on!     -Go, go, go
Let's go!
Fuck. C'mon!
Go! You first. C'mon!
Come on! Stand up!
Stand! Stand up! Come on!
Stand up!
You little fucker.
I'm gonna take your fucking head off!
Dude, you should definitely stand up now!
No!
Stay there.
Fuck!
-You think you could get through me?     -Come on, Max! Come on!
I'm just getting started.
Come on.
Don't give up now. Get up, come! Come on!
You want more than this? I know you.
You look a little bit dizzy, eh?
Did I get you?
Are you bleeding? You must get that looked at.
Hey, boy?
You wanna heal that little girl?
You just need to come through me.
You got some fire in you, boy.
You almost had me.
We die together, boy.
Come on, man, let's go.
Let's go, man, let's do it. Come on!
Ready? Let's go.
Get the guards, now!
Alright.
This'll do it.
Hurry.
OK, we're good, we're good.
We're good.
What?
Max.
It's OK. I know.
There's no coming back from this.
No med-bay can heal you.
Alright, give it to me.
Take it.
OK.
You just have to press that button.
Frey?
Max? Max where are you?
I'm gonna have to break my promise.
I can't make it back up there.
You remember what I said when we were kids?
Yes.
I'll take us there one day.
-Really?     -Yeah, I promise.
You wouldn't believe what I'm looking at right now.
Tell Matilda I really liked her story.
I figured out why the Hippo did it.
Come on!
You go first. Come on!
We all have something special, Max.
Something we're destined to do.
Something for which we were born.
Fuck you!
Let go of me!
Come on, please.
My baby. My dear.
Stand down, Officers.
Arrest him.
I can not arrest a citizen of Elysium.
What?
Doing a great job.
Guess who Elysium belongs to now?
See how beautiful it looks to us down here?
Now look how beautiful we look from up there.
Now it belongs to you.
So you'll never forget where you come from.
My little Max.
極  樂  世  界
21世紀末期地球上疾病肆虐 污染嚴重 人口極劇過剩
地球上最富有的居民 為了維持他們的生活方式 離開了這個星球
洛杉磯 , 2154年
洛杉磯市醫院
安全漏洞 飛船密碼報失
國民合作局
公民 C·查維茲 女性
檢測到多重綜合骨折
門故障
檢測到器官組織
協議
核心更新 M·克魯格特工 開除
協議重啟 編譯
序列完成
是否要保護數據
是
選擇A-癱瘓 選擇B-致死
致死
人腦上傳準備就緒
卡萊爾 我來了
彈藥編碼
已填彈
阿姆達因公司
引爆
鎖定目標
正在填彈
同步完成
協議重啟
信號干擾
可能目標身份確認
麥克斯·達·科斯塔
信號干擾
接近警告 一艘無照飛船正在靠近
顱面復原
完成
公民資格授權   人口：非法移民   人口：合法公民
下載數據將導致載體死亡
系統重啟
阿姆達因
核心更新
新公民 >>> 已增加
公民 瑪蒂爾達·聖蒂亞歌
檢測到急性淋巴細胞白血病
100%清除
新公民需要醫療救助
計算中...
派遣急救飛船去地球提供醫療服務
麥克斯！
快過來！
別讓姐妹們等著
這是芙蕾
她也是新來的
你識字嗎？
這是長頸鹿，是從非洲來的
是的
那裡有很多機器僕人，從早到晚為你服務
如果你住在那裡，你永遠不會生病也不會變老
有一天我會帶大家去那裡
-真的嗎？  -對，我保證
芙蕾和麥克斯
永遠是朋友
麥克斯，你是不是又偷東西了？
太讓我傷心了，你幹嗎要這樣？
為了存錢嗎？
你想有一天買張票去那裡？
那裡不是你能去的，我也是
但這不公平，嬤嬤
我為什麼不能去？
有時候我們沒法理解
我們只能接受這一切
但我知道一件事
我知道你很特別
有一天你會幹一件大事
你就是為這而生的
我的小麥克斯
你好啊，夥計！
去上班啊，每天早起去流水線上工作
去讓世界變得更好嗎？
真是太好笑了，我得上班，太好笑了
得了，孩子！你覺得我有錢嗎？
我看起來像有錢人嗎？
那你呢，你有錢嗎？
來吧，讓我看看你有什麼？
等一下
有五塊錢，太好了，我有五塊錢！我發財了
我終於能買張去極樂世界的船票了？
那是我的
請按次序排隊，你們的車已經來了
我沒帶東西
檢查過了，往前走
早上好，警官
大量犯罪前科，多項重罪，背包裡是什麼？
基本上都是美髮工具
不，我逗你呢…
嘿…我是去上班，夥計，背包裡什麼也沒有
行了，那是我的…
輕罪，不服從指揮
我只是去上班，夥計
-通過  -沒東西，是吧？
零容忍政策適用於所有公民
沒事了吧？
你要立即報告你的假釋官
謝謝你，公民
不，謝謝你
芙蕾，二號床，骨折，謝謝
麥克斯？
芙蕾…
我還以為你在…
-什麼時候回來的？  -我回來有一陣子了
-你好像沒怎麼變  -不，這次不是我的錯
當然不是
-讓我看看  -怎麼樣？
骨折很嚴重
你真的當上護士了！
是啊
真是太好了
你還在偷車嗎？
不，天哪，我早就不幹那些傻事了
我在阿姆達因工作，做流水線，從基層幹起…
-芙蕾，三樓那邊要你去  -馬上就去
-現在既然你回來了…  -等一下
麥克斯，稍等
多明尼加，你能照顧一下這裡嗎？
嘿，聽著，既然現在你回來了
麥克斯，對不起，我得走了
很高興見到你，別惹麻煩了
我沒有
聽著…
我明白，我知道你為什麼離開那裡，我瞭解
如果我像你一樣聰明，我也會閃人
一起吃晚飯吧，僅僅是…
要不喝咖啡也行
-不  -天哪
我得再弄斷條胳膊，才能引起你的注意嗎？
-別這樣  -…我真會這麼做
我的生活很複雜，麥克斯
我只是，我…我很想你
-我星期三晚上八點下班，行了吧？  -好的
-喝咖啡  -喝咖啡，很好
快走吧
所有假釋犯必須通過武器核查
你好
開始之前，我想解釋一下…
麥克斯·達·科斯塔，今天在34-B公共汽車站，違反了刑法第2219條
是的，我就是想跟你說這件事
這其實是個誤會
假釋期延長八個月
等等，什麼？不，不，我能解釋是怎麼回事
我開了個玩笑，然後，你知道的…
不要再說了
警官記錄了暴力和反社會行為
很遺憾必須延長假釋期
檢測到心率加快
-要吃顆藥嗎？  -不用了！
謝謝，我想解釋一下…
不要再說了
性格分析顯示會有78.3%的幾率回復到舊的行為模式
偷竊高級車，用致命武器襲擊
拒捕
-你想和人類談談嗎？  -不，我沒事，謝謝
-你的口氣是在挖苦還是辱罵？  -沒有
辱罵假釋官是一項重罪
我知道
嘿，達·科斯塔！
-你上班遲到了  -對，夥計，我碰到點小麻煩…
不，不，這樣不能工作，你走吧
不，不，我很好，夥計，我能工作
這沒什麼，這個等一下就能拆了，我沒事了
-你沒事？  -我沒事！
好吧，那扣你半天工資
-好的，行吧  -能幹這活算你運氣好
沒有檢測到武器，你可以進入
請保持工作站的整潔
整潔的工作站才是有效率的工作站
快看啊，夥計，他好像長得像你
他的臉做過換膚手術了，看上去不錯
注意：所有工人必須完成每周的指標
請向你的上級報告一切不安全行為
如果我們找不到方法提升股價
我們的投資者會對我們失去信心的
你覺得我跑到地球上來幹什麼？
你以為我喜歡呼吸這裡的空氣嗎？
-不，當然了，不過…  -我能做的都已經做了…
就是為了讓公司恢復營利
這公司還是我一手建立的
現在，我要失陪了
我沒法再和你們談下去了，謝謝
34號關閉！
34號點火
快給她做身份證！
快快快，我們時間不多了
三艘飛船已準備好了，蜘蛛
好的，放到螢幕上
密碼通過了
啟動飛船
我們要上去了！
-歡迎光臨  -你好，夫人
-去看看花園吧  -我們會的，謝謝
-你好，德拉古夫人  -你好
天哪，都長這麼大了
嗨，最近好嗎？
-挺好的，孩子們都來了？  -對，和多明尼加在一起
我有份禮物要送給你，想看看嗎？在沙龍裏面
跟媽媽一起去拿吧
-在沙發邊上  -太好了
再見
夫人，要不要提提神？
命令已經取消了
抱歉打擾您，夫人，我們發現有幾艘無照飛船入境
午安，國防部長德拉古
三級警報三艘無照飛船正在靠近極樂世界領空
六號，七號緊急命令生效
22/B39號協議正在運行
注意外來飛船
你們未經許可擅自進入極樂世界領空
-爸爸！  -沒事的！
立即回到地球，否則我們將採取行動
你們違反了極樂世界的規定
普通警告沒有用
距離我們一萬五千公里，還在靠近…
-我們該怎麼辦，夫人？  -啟動克魯格
夫人，根據355號行政命令，我們沒被授權啟用地球上的資產
我正在授權給你
是，夫人
特工32A，數據包發給你了
歡迎，克魯格特工！
他們距離我們一萬公里，還在靠近
發送飛船坐標
同步目標數據
把他們打下來！
批准執行，21-B，批准執行
導彈已發射！
見鬼
偵測到導彈鎖定，彈著預備，十…
八…七…六…
五…四…三…
二…一…
擊毀兩艘飛船，共有四十六人死亡
導彈五秒後到達…
-最後一枚導彈沒打中  -真可笑！
只有一艘進去了
夫人，飛船已經衝進我們的大氣層
第一艘無照飛船著陸了
把那艘船上所有的人都給我抓起來
身份確認
掃瞄
啟動重建程序
不！
我們逮捕了32人，13人死亡，還有兩個非法移民在逃，夫人
身體重建完成
你們因觸犯68-C移民法案被逮捕！
-所有非法移民已被拘捕，夫人  -好的
送他們去驅逐部
德拉古部長，請立即向帕特爾總統匯報
德拉古部長，請向帕特爾總統匯報
你好，夥計？怎麼了？
跟平常一樣，因為警察
-你沒事吧？  -沒事，不用擔心
麥克斯，我跟你說件事，聽著…
-不！  -什麼『不』？
你都沒聽我說完呢
-行了，說吧  -好的
你知道山上洛斯齊塔斯的房子嗎？
知道，他們有很多槍
是的，他們有五輛車，都是新的
我們三個去，明天午飯的時候
-午飯的時候  -就這計劃？
我的天哪
-你有更好的主意嗎？  -對，我們帶上一個人
太陽出來前就去，你們偷那兩輛最快的車
把另幾輛車的電池
你耍我，去死吧！
你上當了！
求求你，夥計，你是最棒的，給我一年，就一年
-我不想再回監獄了  -就一年，求求你！
看看你，你以前是傳奇人物，現在呢？
現在時間上午5點50分
沒有檢測到武器，你可以進入
34號關門！
注意，門沒對齊，工人將會…
嘿，你拖慢進度了
不，我的機器卡住了！
注意:工人們每班上洗手間不能超過一次…
-你幹了什麼？達·科斯塔？  -沒有，我只是讓門重新啟動
讓我看看
-擠到棧板了  -對，位置動了
-你進去  -不，我是說…
聽著，要嘛你現在進去…
要嘛我找其他人，然後你就捲鋪蓋走人
-拜託，夥計  -不，不，我沒開玩笑，懂嗎？
快進去！
快點，夥計們，快回去工作！
見鬼
不，不，不，停下！
嘿！
嘿，快走開，危險！
太晚了！
把他弄出來！
我有一個夢想，嬤嬤
我只是想住在那裡
從我們這裡看那裡很美是吧？
是的
好，現在…
從那裡看我們這裡也很美
留著吧
現在是你的了
永遠不要忘了你是從哪裡來的
出了什麼事？
你受到了致命劑量的輻射
你的器官將會嚴重衰竭
五天後你就會死
出了什麼事？為什麼停工？
-他被輻射了  -別朝我呼氣
-把嘴捂上  -對不起，先生
他的皮膚脫落嗎？還是什麼？
我可不想把床換掉，快把他弄出去
-是，先生  -好，謝謝
卡萊爾先生，您的飛船準備出發了
請簽名接受藥物治療
米珀洛，超強效
能在你死前維持器官正常運作
每頓飯吃一粒
感謝你的服務
昨天下午三點你擊落兩艘飛船，殺死了四十六個平民
你處理非法移民應該儘可能低調
我已經意識到了
另外你使用的這個…特工
M·克魯格先生
有十五次侵犯人權…
強姦、綁架、刑求逼供
這個人已經被確診有嚴重心理問題
我們已經明確告訴過你，我們不再用潛伏的特工了
跟我說說，帕特爾總統
你有孩子嗎？
接受審查的是你不是我
那我假設你沒有
如果你有孩子
也許你會表現得更有益於…
延長我們這個地方的使用壽命
我的想法和做法現在已經過時了
這我心裏很清楚
但是當他們來到你家…
你為你的孩子建造的家…
和你孩子的孩子…
靠公關和競選承諾是趕不走那些人的
只能靠我！
我聽夠了！這是最後的警告
如果妳再自作主張行動，妳就會被解職
讓我們永久性地開除克魯格特工吧
全都贊成？
很好，立即生效
來點啤酒嗎？
你已經被國民合作局開除了
請去當地大使館退還所有武器
該死的政治！去死吧！
等我一下…
麥克斯…
麥克斯！
你怎麼了？發生什麼事？
天哪，我來幫你，進屋去吧
麥克斯，怎麼回事？
-麥克斯，怎麼回事？  -我不該進去的
到哪去？
我受到致命劑量的輻射
致命劑量
你會好起來的，我來幫你
-你會好起來的，麥克斯  -他們給了我米珀洛
他們給了我該死的…米珀洛
我只有五天可活了！只有五天！
你得把藥吃了
-極樂世界能治這病  -我知道
-我要去見蜘蛛  -麥克斯，麥克斯！
先把藥吃了！
給你水！
去見蜘蛛，你需要錢
就算我把所有積蓄都給你，也買不起一張票
他會給我一張票
他會給我一張該死的票的
芙蕾，你知道我們已經盡全力救你女兒了
今天我和委員會討論過了
他們建議把你女兒送回家
她在家裡我怎麼還能在這裡工作？
她隨時可能發作，費薩爾醫生
我知道，如果她又發作了，妳就把她帶回來住院，這沒問題
但她現在不能住院
這裡不是極樂世界，我們沒法治好她
麥克斯！
好久不見啊，哥們！
工廠那邊怎麼樣啊？
-我要請你幫個忙  -什麼？我沒聽見，什麼？
我要一張上去的票，和一個身份證
行，當然可以
位子要靠窗的還是靠道的？
我沒跟你開玩笑
聽著，我會回來的，我會回來為你工作
你要什麼都行，我一定會還你的
知道嗎？
這個…可是…
無價的
這個是無價的
我問你個問題
你知道每天有多少笨蛋
跑到這裡來，說跟你同樣的話嗎？
說什麼我有個小孩，他們每天都來
麥克斯，如果我是你，我就馬上離開這裡，懂嗎？
麥克斯，不…
麥克斯，不要…
我為了你坐了三年牢
就憑我為你，做的那些事，你就該送我上去
-感覺到了嗎？  -來吧，殺了我
現在我身體裏都是輻射物
要是濺出來還會輻射到你
-你真的要死了嗎？  -我要死了，混蛋，聽見了嗎？
看見嗎？結束了，把槍放下
把槍放下！把槍放下！都滾出去！
聽到嗎？
聽著，我在找人幫我做一件事
但是我這裡沒人有那個膽量
你說叫你幹什麼都行，對嗎？
麥克斯…
-沒事吧？  -我沒事
這個…
我的朋友
這個就是你上去的票
你最後為我做件事，我就送你上去
什麼事？
一個極樂世界的混蛋，懂嗎？
一個億萬富翁，他下到地球上來做生意…
他來…他來…管他來幹什麼，我們綁架他
-得了！  -放鬆
我的計劃比你想的複雜
我們不要他的錶，不要他的車，這些東西都不要
這個，我們要這個
我們要他腦袋裏的那些有機信息
我說的是銀行代碼、密碼、登陸數據…
靠這些能拿幾億的錢
你要做的就是接通他的大腦，用這東西把數據下載到你的腦子裏
然後帶回來給我
這太瘋狂了，麥克斯
我們一旦核實了數據，我就給你一張免費的單程票
還附送飲料和小吃
到時候你只要走進一間屋子，運行醫療機，你就痊癒了
桑德羅會負責手術，你認識他嗎？
-怎麼回事…  -我的天哪！
我沒事
事實上你看上去虛弱
虛弱得一塌糊塗，所以…
知道嗎，我會讓他們…
這太瘋狂了，我們走吧，聽我的
我還能怎麼辦？
我會讓他們給你裝上這個…
…這是！
第三代外骨盔甲
它會和神經系統連接，讓你和機器人一樣強
準備好做手術了，對嗎？
我們快走吧，拜託
我要一個四人團隊，人我來選
我會派我自己的數據師去
腦對腦數據傳輸很難搞的
不過我要帶上胡力歐，你也要給他一張上去的票，跟我一樣
好，沒問題
好了，我去叫他們過來
等等！
目標得是約翰·卡萊爾
你說的是阿姆達因公司的執行總裁？
對，就是他
德拉古部長，卡萊爾先生來了
你來這裡是想說服我續簽和阿姆達因的合同吧？
你總是這麼聰明
跟我來
我對你那些小想法不感興趣
我感興趣的是更大的東西
這個地方在死去
它的內部得了一種政治病，這顆腫瘤必須剷除掉
你和你的公司，你們的營利越來越少
是…
你造了這個圓環
你能不能重置伺服器，扶植一位新總統上台？
這是政變嗎？
你的意思是要政變？
有可能嗎？
我可以寫個重啟序列？
關掉整個系統到那個時候…
你就能編碼一位新總統了
這就是你要做的事？
如果成功，你們公司就能續簽兩百年的合同
導彈防禦系統、機器人一切用來保護我們自由的東西
你們的新總統，會保證這一切的
你有工作了！卡萊爾先生
就是這個人
-就是他嗎？  -就是他
坐下
我們會切開你的頭
溫柔點，桑德羅，溫柔點
先給他弄個身份證
我們先給他弄個身份證
-是這個嗎？  -對，準備好
手抬起來
我們只有這個
你找到什麼？
這會連接你的DNA
你會融入那裡，就像你是生在那裡的
該動真格的了
夥計
嘿
這會疼嗎？
對，小妞，會有點疼
不過也很爽
手術結束你就會變成貧民區的忍者了
瑪麗安娜！…把骨鋸拿下來
我什麼也聽不見，快把骨鋸拿下來！
你不會弄死我吧？
不會有事的，老兄
麥克斯
我在這裡
我們能成功
是的！
嘿！
他醒了！
你挺過來了？
真沒想到！
你還能打手槍呢？
情況怎麼樣？
他現在很強了？
你對我做了什麼？
給了你一條活路
見鬼
你好，搭檔？
這套裝備感覺怎麼樣？
感覺棒極了！
給我看
給你
這是什麼，傳家寶嗎？
等一下
這是空爆彈
你選定目標…
子彈會在目標周圍爆炸，殺傷半徑五米
還有…
這玩意還配了同步爆破彈
不錯啊
行動吧！
先生…
飛船準備好了
能聽見嗎？
收到
計劃是這樣的
我們在工廠外面等他的飛船起飛
你發一枚爆破彈上去
然後趕到墜毀地點拿數據
好的，明白
好了，開始行動吧！上吧！
你緊張嗎？
-不！  -不？
我都嚇得尿褲子了
-我們不會死在這裡的  -對
上，上，上！
十五秒後將加速到超聲速
快點，快點，快點！
發動機嚴重損壞
一位極樂世界公民在地球遇到危險
馬上顯示資料…
公民身份確認，約翰·卡萊爾，N8321P…
我看見你了，混蛋！
我這裡出了點事
克魯格，能聽到嗎？
德拉古小姐，很高興聽到你的聲音
有個攜帶敏感大腦數據的公民在城外
幾個小偷想搶劫那些數據
什麼數據？
這是機密
你才不會叫一個剛被開除的特工去幫你找什麼該死的機密數據呢
政府不知道這件事，對嗎？
我想要什麼都行，對嗎？
請做好防撞擊準備
請保持冷靜，你承受的損傷為零
真是個好消息啊
我有一個條件，我幹這工作，你得幫我復職
好的
我幫你安排了你喜歡的特工
當然了，完全是保密的，他們馬上就會趕到你那邊
把任務資料發給我
走吧，夥計們，快出來！
機器人，那邊有幾輛某種型號的車，上面有一個…
有兩個人
他們都帶著武器，我要他們死
機器人！
槍卡彈了！
身份確認：麥克斯·達·科斯塔，聯邦假釋號61492-8-557
好了！
它在填彈！
-沒事吧！我們快走，我去開門  -快走，我掩護你們！
快，快，快！
別亂動
拿過來！
那邊還有一個！
去死吧，混蛋！
別打目標！
不，不！他中彈了！
公民受到心胸外傷
血壓正在下降
傷口不在頭上？
-他還有氣嗎？  -有，傷口在胸上
那我們還能工作，幫我托住他的頭
把這個插到你身上，快點
來吧，寶貝，快點！
-好  -有反應嗎？
對，我們在同步
你不知道，自己在做什麼
距離目標一分鐘，長官
行了，同步上了，來吧，寶貝，傳吧
我說能行吧
發生數據搶劫，他們正在下載，已經在傳了
夥計們，有人來了
該死的！
快點，夥計們，快點
那是雷文機，是軍用飛機
-就快好了，百分之97…98  -快點，他們來了
-馬上就好  -99！
搞定，成功了！
見鬼！天哪，數據被破壞了！
等等，等一下
我沒法讀數據，是亂碼！讀不出
什麼？
-快點，夥計們，我們得走了  -『亂碼』是什麼東東？
該死的！
不，不！我們再運行一次！
-放開我，夥計！我放棄了  -求求你，再運行一次
去你的！快點，我們離開這裡
你要去哪裡，桑德羅？
快離開這裡！該死的！
快走，夥計
快離開那裡！
快走！我們快走！
老大，有個逃跑的
開火！
這才是我說的那碼子事！
見鬼！
目標朝南-西南方向移動
快點，麥克斯！它來了！
我們找到另一個
好了！
這計劃錯了！徹底糟透了，夥計！
保持盤旋狀態！
我看你往哪裡跑？
來吧！
見鬼！
該死的！
來吧！
不！
不，不
不！起來！
起來！
不！
一名襲擊者步行逃走了，夫人
他們有數據，重複：
那些小偷搶了數據
不惜一切代價逮捕目標，不要毀壞他的大腦
我們走！有一個跑了！
公民死於失血過多導致的心跳停止
死亡時間17點45分
出來，你躲去哪裡了？
那是什麼？
看上去像是一群豬，老大
該死的！找到他！
送我們回墜機地點，看看他們留下什麼？
明白
謝謝
老大，你最好過來看看這個
這是我們掃瞄到的罪犯
和卡萊爾之間傳輸資料的記錄
怪不得她那麼著急
那傢伙的腦袋裏有打開王國的鑰匙！
我們要找到他
我派姑娘們出去
搜尋網路3到11
我授權了全面封鎖
把洛杉磯定為禁飛區
-整個洛杉磯嗎？  -兇手還逍遙法外
逮捕到他之前，不許有任何人離開那座城
搞什麼…？
麥克斯
-嗨，親愛的！  -嗨
我們可以回家了
我的病好了嗎？
我去開車，好嗎？
我馬上就回來
芙蕾…
麥克斯！
我的天哪，你怎麼了？
-見鬼，我去叫醫生  -不，不！
-我不能進去  -麥克斯！
-我不能進去…  -麥克斯，聽我說，你得看醫生，明白嗎？
有人在找我，他們要殺我
-我來這裡是找你的，我需要你幫忙  -麥克斯！
接受治療得走系統程序
求你救救我，我不想死
麥克斯！
別睡著！
-我想看看那個人  -媽媽會救他的，好嗎？
你快睡覺
別睡著！
你實在是太重了，麥克斯，幫幫我！
起來！
麥克斯，你行的！
別睡著，翻個身！
麥克斯，麥克斯，等等
-謝謝  -誰把你弄成這樣的？
我不知道，我…我工作時受傷了
我只好去幫蜘蛛工作，這樣才能到上面去治病
但事情搞糟了，我麻煩大了
媽媽？
寶貝，過來！
這人是誰？
他叫麥克斯，媽媽跟你一樣大時就認識他了
-這是瑪蒂爾達  -嗨！
你去看動畫片吧，好嗎？
我一會就來
我不知道你有…對不起，我該走了
-等等，麥克斯，等等，你不能走  -我不該來的，我得離開了
麥克斯！她快死了，她已經到了白血病晚期
我說過我的生活很複雜，我需要你幫我
-但我不知道該怎麼做  -做什麼？
-帶她去極樂世界  -我幫不了她，我…
如果可以我一定會的
那這個呢，假公民身份，如果你帶她上去
-能用這個幫她治病嗎？  -那樣沒用的
這是我的編碼，是跟我的DNA鎖定的
那些找我的人，他們是…你不明白這些人是誰
一旦他們找到我，會把我們全都殺了
我唯一能幫你的就是離開這裡，我向你發誓
-她是我的一切  -對不起
你身上綁著繃帶
對，我綁著繃帶
你在幹什麼？
我不希望你生病，你想聽故事嗎？
什麼，不…
很久以前有一隻貓鼬住在叢林裏
它肚子很餓，但它太小了
非常小
其他大的動物都有食物吃，因為它們能摘到水果
於是它去和一隻河馬交朋友
行了，別說了！
這隻貓鼬結局很慘吧？
不，不是這樣的，因為它可以站在河馬的背上
摘到所有它想要的水果
-河馬有什麼好處呢？  -河馬想要一個朋友
對不起
老大
找到他了
馬上著陸
-媽媽，出什麼事了嗎？  -沒事的，寶貝
安全！
這是什麼？
午安
很抱歉突然闖進你家，這並不意味著…
我不是故意要嚇到你的小女兒的
我和我的手下是來這裡找一位先生…
他不久前就在這房子裏
希望你能告訴我們他去哪裡了
不
我…
-我不知道他去哪裡了  -我不喜歡…
…在孩子面前使用暴力
所以我要請你閉上眼睛，親愛的
-沒事的，寶貝  -我真的需要你告訴我
嘿？
-想起來了嗎？  -媽媽！
閉上眼睛，把你該死的眼睛閉上
讓她閉上眼睛
求求你，我不知道他在哪裡
他受傷了，我救了他，然後他走了
求求你！
你瞧瞧，這年頭都沒人講義氣了？
那是什麼？
-你這裡開了個醫院嗎？  -她生病了
她生病了嗎？讓我看看她…行嗎？
-別碰她  -看見嗎？這是保護的本能！
我說了不要碰她！
我只是想跟她說幾句話
不要碰她！
-帶上她，來吧！  -你要帶我們去哪裡？
-我有你想要的東西  -別害怕，寶貝
沒事的，寶貝
給我坐下！閉上嘴！
站住！
不，不，別殺他！把槍放下！讓他過來！
-你拿到了什麼東西，對嗎？  -什麼？
所以他們會封鎖領空…為了什麼？
銀行電匯？軍事情報？一定是什麼重要的東西！
沒有，我什麼也沒弄到！
全都是亂碼，胡力歐死了，你欠我個人情，我們快去上面吧！
去不了！他們干擾了飛行系統信號！
沒有人能上得去
-什麼時候能恢復？  -我怎麼知道？
-我一定要到上面去！  -所有人都要到上面去
我的人在想辦法
看是不是能有機會上線
不過，現在呢…
讓我先看看你腦袋裏的東西
別碰我，夥計！
看著我，如果他們封鎖整個領空
只是為了你腦袋裏的東西…
那麼讓他們開放領空的鑰匙可能也在那裡面，對嗎？
來吧
好了
為了這個，他們追到天邊也要抓到你
這是什麼？
這是極樂世界的重啟程序
誰擁有了這個，就能改寫極樂世界的整個系統
開放邊界…
讓所有人都成為極樂世界的公民
這東西能救你的命
-能救所有人  -我什麼時候能走？
我的人想混進去關掉信號干擾，應該很快能搞定…
-別扯淡了，我們什麼時候能走？  -我不知道
五天吧…一周？
見鬼去吧，我根本活不了五天！我只能活幾個小時
我的人在努力
你總是在努力，但總是沒辦法送我上去
我都不明白，你幹嗎要想辦法送人上去？
他們只會被打死
但有了那個就不同了，情況不一樣了！
我們能控制系統，我們能說了算！
我們能徹底改變這該死的歷史了！
回到剛才說的
我腦子裏的東西對他們來說很重要，對嗎？
不要這樣
如果它落到壞人手裏，他們會把我們永遠隔絕在外
聽著，夥計，我現在就要上去
如果你能找到我，我也治好了病，我就把東西都給你
-我不想死在這裡  -你這樣不對，麥克斯，別這樣
別開槍！別開槍！
沒事的，沒事的
我一直想找個老婆
但就是一直沒法安定下來，你知道的？誘惑太多了
可是你…
你讓我想要安定下來
你真的讓我想安定下來，寶貝
-該死的，長官  -什麼？
你最好過來看看
-幹嗎？怎麼回事？  -看看這該死的橡樹
帶我們下去
-接著  -是的，長官
把門打開
別過來，你們得照我說的做
否則我把自己腦袋炸了，明白嗎？
好的！
我腦袋裏的東西都能給你！
只要你帶我上去，給我用醫療機
-我掌握的東西很有價值  -我們能幫你治療
給你用醫療機，這些問題都能解決
走吧！我們帶你上去
上面天氣不錯，空氣又好又乾淨，你會喜歡那裡的
-別想動歪腦筋！  -上來吧！
見見我的弟兄，來吧！
別害羞，他們不會傷害你的
我來給你介紹，這位是德雷克，這是麥克斯
你好，猛男？
我們走！
是的，夫人，我們已經逮捕了目標
-打開領空，我們要回家了  -我們十九分鐘後見
-取消禁飛區  -是，夫人
等等…
等一下，那是什麼？…
網絡恢復了嗎？馬塞羅！這是怎麼回事？恢復了嗎？
我們連上線了，蜘蛛
芙蕾…
對不起，我會搞定的
-我們找到他了  -好的，他在哪裡？
他在離開地球…去極樂世界
曼紐爾！黎戈！帶上武器！我們到上面去
EL234請求在22區著陸
收到，EL234，批准你們進入
-我看到你有G-1手雷  -行了，給我退後
-要不然呢？  -我就引爆它
你想怎麼樣？
我要你腦袋裏的東西，孩子，殺死他！
抓住他！
我們要怎麼做，夫人？
我要國土安全局逮捕所有從裏面走出來的人
把安全許可級別在五級以下的人全部清出這棟樓
我警告過你的
剛才一艘無照的飛船墜毀了，對這裡是潛在的威脅
會發生這種事都是因為你的無能，帶他出去
-別碰我  -這屬於戰爭行為
這種情況下國民合作局由我來控制
現在我要去工作了
我肯定你要去參加一個籌款活動
走吧，先生
麥克斯！
快幫我下來，麥克斯！
我在想辦法！
空氣質量達到中毒狀態
快幫我下來！
建議您立即離開這艘飛船
快跑！
見鬼！
兩個非法移民在第三區朝東北方去
你去抓那兩個，我來對付這個混蛋
歡迎參觀這棟壯觀的豪宅，它佔地…
錯誤
不要啊！
未探測到公民
求求你，她生病了，幫幫我們，她已經昏迷了
求求你！
我們是不是該弄掉這些東西？
不行，我們得先弄到數據
這和他的神經系統連在一起
數據沒有受損吧？
看上去是的
警告
我們可以把數據取出來，不過他會死
無所謂了
你們下載數據，讓系統恢復正常要多長時間？
不用很久，夫人
所有資料都保留在機密雲裏，禁止一切訪問
馬上開始準備
把那兩個弄走
明白
科特，想去抓老大的女人嗎？
好的，夥計
採取機動迴避
讓他們白忙一場
找到了！
我們走！
行了，50位元組，哥們，準備好了嗎？
你要從他身上拿什麼？
你想對他幹什麼？
他會怎麼樣？
該起床了
-起來！  -麥克斯
麥克斯，麥克斯，麥克斯！
給我進去！
是的，老大搞砸了，呃？
吃了個該死的手雷，呃！
他的大腦沒事，不過他醒過來一定會氣瘋的
還記得上次他在印度掉了條胳膊嗎？
克魯格
老大？
我是克洛
他在哪裡？
行了，準備好了，再打次鎮靜劑
準備好注射器，你抓住這個？
抓住針頭！抓住針頭！抓住…
-他們把姑娘們帶哪裡去了？  -去軍械庫了
那地方在哪裡？
在第三層
檢測到致命放射性中毒，你需要立即接受治療
你這個笨蛋！知道自己幹了什麼嗎？
你在城郊撞毀了一艘無照飛船
我給你的命令是秘密行動
你還記得這是什麼意思嗎？
你是不是瘋了？你現在已經沒用了
如果政府意識到我們在做什麼
會以叛國罪把我們吊死
看在上帝的份上，克魯格！你在聽我說話嗎？
是的
是的，夫人
我在聽
很抱歉，我們的飛船墜毀弄壞了那些車輛和人家的草坪
沒人能以叛國罪吊死我們
現在我們說了算！
把手放在上面，用力壓住
你現在很難受了吧？
好了，孩子們！極樂世界終於要有個稱職的總統了
她需要醫療
我本來想治好你女兒的
不過，現在我要確保她永遠不會被治好
德雷克，永遠別信政治家說的話！
把這棟樓清乾淨！
謝謝，老大
我要找到那個小流氓
拿到他腦袋裏的東西，這裡現在是我的了
你敢跑到我家裏來玩！
那就玩吧！
我要幹掉那個小混蛋
嘿！
這是怎麼回事？
所有國民合作局的人員，請從最近的出口離開，冷靜地前往底層…
快點，快走！
不
不用
公民死亡
現在啟動緊急系統
請根據指示行動
蜘蛛！
你能聽到嗎？
麥克斯，你在哪裡？
我腦袋裏的東西，能讓所有人成為這裡的公民，對嗎？
對
你知道怎麼把它弄出來，對嗎？
你確定嗎？
是的，我確定
好，你仔細聽我說
已選擇軍械庫
好了
幫我啟動
克洛，把那兩個處理掉
樂意效勞，老大，樂意效勞
你在哪裡？小子，你在哪裡？
你好啊，小妞？
玩玩吧
-來吧，我會很好，很溫柔的，我保證  -不，求求你
-來吧  -離我遠點！
-你希望我傷害這個姑娘嗎？  -不！
那就給我過來
見鬼！
她還活著嗎？
目前還活著
待在我後面
我帶你們出去
我有個計劃
你聽到這聲音嗎？
這是我來找你的聲音
我會找到你！我會宰了你！
芙蕾，我們得分頭行動
-什麼？  -聽著
你到地面上去，行嗎？拿著這個
找個房子，給她用醫療機
-不，沒用的  -別停下，別停下…
她沒有身份證，沒法用醫療機
這次一定能行，我有辦法搞定
-已選擇地面  -快去
跟我一起走
-我一會就來  -不
我保證
有個媽媽帶著女兒剛才進了那邊的電梯
她們要到地面上去找醫療機
你派個人護送她們到那裡
我就履行諾言
直接去醫療機
-我們走  -快走
-快走，快點！  -過來這邊！
快點夥計
…啟動緊急封鎖…
快到了，快到了
怎麼啦？
只不過是點…皮肉傷！
這樣才像話嘛
偵測到火災…
離開門！離開門！
…門都已經關閉
-開了！快走！  -快快快
我們快走
該死的門！快開
快！你先走，快點！
快起來！站起來！
快起來！快起來！快點！
快起來！
你這個臭雜種
我要把你該死的頭擰下來！
夥計，你現在一定要站起來！
不！
待在這裡
見鬼！
-你以為你能打敗我嗎？  -加油，麥克斯！加油！
我才剛開始呢
起來
別這麼快就放棄，起來！快點！
你不止這點本事？我知道的
你是不是有點頭暈啊？
我劃傷你了嗎？
你在流血，你得去看醫生
夥計？
你想治好那個小女孩？
你得先過我這關
你小子還有點本事的
你差點打敗我
我們同歸於盡吧
好了，我們快走
我們快去吧，快！
準備好了？我們走吧
別讓門關上！
行了
來幹吧
快點
可以開始了，可以開始了
可以開始了
什麼？
麥克斯
沒關係，我知道
無法再回頭了
醫療機也治不好
行了，把鍵盤給我
拿著
好
你只要按那個按鈕
芙蕾？
麥克斯？麥克斯你在哪裡？
我沒法實現我的承諾了
我到不了你那邊了
記得我們小時候我說的話嗎？
記得
有一天我會帶大家去那裡
-真的嗎？  -是的，我保證
你不會相信我現在看到了什麼？
告訴瑪蒂爾達，我很喜歡她講的故事
我明白了為什麼河馬會這麼做
來吧！
你先來，來啊！
每個人都有自己的才能，麥克斯
一件他們注定要做的事
一件他們為之而生的事
去死吧！
放開我！
快點，求求你
我的寶貝，我親愛的
解除戰備，警官
逮捕他
我不能逮捕極樂世界的公民
什麼？
夥計，幹得好
猜猜極樂世界現在歸誰了？
從我們這裡看那裡很美是嗎？
從那裡看我們這裡也很美
現在是你的了
永遠不要忘了你是從哪裡來的
我的小麥克斯
字
字幕
字幕製
字幕製作
字幕製作 ★
字幕製作 ★ 至
字幕製作 ★ 至宏
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上人